http://www.fuk.co.uk/privacy/

Privacy policy
fuk.co.uk respects your privacy.
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of fuk.co.uk. The only exception to this is for competition entries, where you have the option to opt out of the competition sponsor receiving your email address.
Credit card details
fuk.co.uk will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on fuk.co.uk.
External Sites.
fuk.co.uk is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows fuk.co.uk to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and fuk.co.uk does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to fuk.co.uk and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through fuk.co.uk have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
fuk.co.uk is made by Wide Media. For any other information, please contact us here.
Username:
Password:
or register
report this ad
Active
Classifieds
Who's Online?
Winter Jackets / Coats!The Dead Celeb ThreadProperty threadPolitics threadThe Running ThreadLast Purchase (PICS thread, your OWN pic...What 'Claire Rayners' Are You Wearing Or...Online Store ReviewsCyclingMIA threadThe Knitwear Thread!ebay & paypal queries and questions thre...Which watch?Official holiday threadPentonvilles Jesus Juice/Natural Wine th...What are you wearing 2020Shoes and Boots threadWANTS -- Post Your Wants In Here ROYAL MAILHave A Baby By Me, Baby Be A Millionaire...
FS: Our Legacy & South2 West8 iPhone XS 256GB £420 / Converse Polka Do...orSlow Fatigue shirtSupreme striped top&sacred hearts Oxford...Emergency sale. Nike, RRL redwings addedNike ACG thick cotton cargo pantsPolo Ralph Military M65 SmallAdidas PureBoost DPR - Uniqlo USandro leather, H&M Studio 2016 Suede ja...Garmin Forerunner 735XTFDMTL Patchwork faded selvedge jeansAspesi - Sandro FS: Gitman, Woolrich, Engineered Garment...Black Uniqlo +J Hybrid Down Parka Oversi...Please deleteFinal Drop - Nanamica Harbor Down JacketIPhone X - 256gb SOLD
SoldOur Legacy bomber 50/large
ct, MrW, mike-s, niccodea, swede, Ulster_Blue, generic_guy, Robadob, morgan, Ocin
Forums
MenswearWomenswearRandom Fashion QuestionsGeneral DiscussionRandom QuestionsClassifiedsTech HelpArchive
© 1995-2018 Wide Media.
